<resources>
    <string name="app_name">android-walkthrough-with-oop</string>

    <string name="next">Next</string>

    <string name="step_1">Step 1</string>
    <string name="step_2">Step 2</string>
    <string name="step_3">Step 3</string>
    <string name="step_4">Step 4</string>
    <string name="step_5">Step 5</string>
    <string name="step_6">Step 6</string>
    <string name="step_7">Step 7</string>
    <string name="step_8">Step 8</string>
    <string name="step_9">Step 9</string>

    <string name="pasta_1">Start Your Dough</string>
    <string name="pasta_2">Whisk and Knead The Dough</string>
    <string name="pasta_3">Let The Dough Rest</string>
    <string name="pasta_4">Divide The Dough</string>
    <string name="pasta_5">Roll The Dough</string>
    <string name="pasta_6">Keep Rolling</string>
    <string name="pasta_7">Slice Noodles</string>
    <string name="pasta_8">Loosen The Noodles</string>
    <string name="pasta_9">Cook The Noodles</string>

    <string name="captain_american">Captain American</string>
    <string name="hulk">Hulk</string>
    <string name="spider_man">Spider Man</string>
    <string name="iron_man">Iron Man</string>
    <string name="wolverine">Wolverine</string>
    <string name="dead_pool">Dead Pool</string>
    <string name="thor">Thor</string>

    <string name="captain_american_description">Captain America is a fictional character appearing in American comic books published by Marvel Comics. Created by cartoonists Joe Simon and Jack Kirby, the character first appeared in Captain America Comics #1 (cover dated March 1941) from Timely Comics, a predecessor of Marvel Comics. Captain America was designed as a patriotic supersoldier who often fought the Axis powers of World War II and was Timely Comics\' most popular character during the wartime period. The popularity of superheroes waned following the war and the Captain America comic book was discontinued in 1950, with a short-lived revival in 1953. Since Marvel Comics revived the character in 1964, Captain America has remained in publication.</string>
    <string name="hulk_description">The Hulk is a fictional superhero appearing in American comic books published by Marvel Comics. Created by writer Stan Lee and artist Jack Kirby, the character first appeared in the debut issue of The Incredible Hulk (May 1962). In his comic book appearances, the character is both the Hulk, a green-skinned, hulking and muscular humanoid possessing a vast degree of physical strength, and his alter ego Bruce Banner, a physically weak, socially withdrawn, and emotionally reserved physicist, the two existing as personalities independent and resenting of the other.</string>
    <string name="spider_man_description">Spider-Man is a fictional superhero appearing in American comic books published by Marvel Comics. The character was created by writer-editor Stan Lee and writer-artist Steve Ditko, and first appeared in the anthology comic book Amazing Fantasy #15 (Aug. 1962) in the Silver Age of Comic Books. Lee and Ditko conceived the character as an orphan being raised by his Aunt May and Uncle Ben, and as a teenager, having to deal with the normal struggles of adolescence in addition to those of a costumed crime-fighter. Spider-Man\'s creators gave him super strength and agility, the ability to cling to most surfaces, shoot spider-webs using wrist-mounted devices of his own invention, which he calls "web-shooters", and react to danger quickly with his "spider-sense", enabling him to combat his foes.</string>
    <string name="iron_man_description">Iron Man (Anthony Edward "Tony" Stark) is a fictional superhero appearing in American comic books published by Marvel Comics. The character was created by writer and editor Stan Lee, developed by scripter Larry Lieber, and designed by artists Don Heck and Jack Kirby. The character made his first appearance in Tales of Suspense #39 (cover dated March 1963).</string>
    <string name="wolverine_description">Wolverine (born James Howlett commonly known as Logan and sometimes as Weapon X) is a fictional character appearing in American comic books published by Marvel Comics, mostly in association with the X-Men. He is a mutant who possesses animal-keen senses, enhanced physical capabilities, powerful regenerative ability known as a healing factor, and three retractable bone claws in each hand. Wolverine has been depicted variously as a member of the X-Men, Alpha Flight, and the Avengers.</string>
    <string name="dead_pool_description">Deadpool (Wade Winston Wilson) is a fictional antihero appearing in American comic books published by Marvel Comics. Created by artist/writer Rob Liefeld and writer Fabian Nicieza, the character first appeared in The New Mutants #98 (cover-dated February 1991). Initially Deadpool was depicted as a supervillain when he made his first appearance in The New Mutants and later in issues of X-Force, but later evolved into his more recognizable antiheroic persona. Deadpool, whose real name is Wade Wilson, is a disfigured and mentally unstable mercenary with the superhuman ability of an accelerated healing factor and physical prowess. The character is known as the "Merc with a Mouth" because of his talkative nature and tendency to break the fourth wall, which is used by writers for humorous effect and running gags.</string>
    <string name="thor_description">Thor Odinson is a fictional superhero appearing in American comic books published by Marvel Comics. The character, based on the Norse mythological deity of the same name, is the Asgardian god of thunder and possesses the enchanted hammer Mjolnir, which grants him the ability of flight and weather manipulation amongst his other superhuman attributes.</string>
</resources>
